Liudmila Mashkina

Software Engineer

Phone: 425-502-2550 LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/liudmila-mashkina-b4a10369/

My website: http://liudmila-mashkina-2049812041.us-west-2.elb.amazonaws.com/

email: liudmilamashkina@gmail.com



Software developer with 2+ years of experience on own product. Communicative quick learner with a huge teamwork experience, seeking to progress everyday. I have already developed cross-platform C++ game and just built and published a personal website, created from scratch and hosted on AWS.

Experience

Oct 2015 - present

Self-employed Software Engineer

Personal Website

Link: http://liudmila-mashkina-2049812041.us-west-2.elb.amazonaws.com/Source: https://github.com/LiudmilaMashkina/Website

Responsible for end-to-end development:

- Built Python Web Server
- Deployed the site to AWS EC2
- Built the site using HTML/CSS/JavaScript
- · Implemented flexible layout supporting mobile devices and large screens

Runner

Cross-platform C++ game

Demo: http://liudmila-mashkina-2049812041.us-west-2.elb.amazonaws.com/

Source: https://github.com/LiudmilaMashkina/Runner

Responsible for end-to-end development:

- · App architecture
- System design
- Implemented full game logic using C++ on top of Box2D, Cocos2d
- · Setup multiplatform build using CMake
- · Setup resource export from Blender using Python
- Build UI framework on top of Cocos2d
- · Setup version control using Git and Bitbucket

Sept 2012 - Feb 2015

Fashion Designer

Ltd. Bosco Sport - Moscow, Russia

- Leading designer on Russian Olympic and Paralympic teams sport uniform for all seasons from FW 2013-2014 and till FW 2015-2016.
- · Created uniforms for different Sochi 2014 Olympic Games purposes (Bibs, Flower ceremonies and etc.)
- · Collaborated in creation of corporate sport uniforms for many big Russian companies
- · Trained and mentored junior designers.

Education

Sept 2006 - May 2012

Moscow State University of Design and Technology (MSU DT)

- Master
- · Fashion Designer
- · Diploma with honors
- Participated in several side projects with our professors in the area of Costume history.

Skills

- Strong C++ 2 years of experience working on real project, end to end.
- Python used Python scripting for importing models from Blender, website backend and console apps, like auto image generator.
- Strong algorithmic background.
- · Strong OOP understanding.
- · Software design.
- JSON used for transferring data between different parts of project.
- XML- learned during game dev, but gave preference to JSON.
- HTML wrote personal website.
- · CSS used for styling my site.
- · Basic JavaScript customizing site layout, supporting right scaling.
- · Basic **¡Query**
- · Bash/Zsh constantly used for grepping, software installation using macports, running scripts.